Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series III. Project Records
  - Contracts
    - Boise-Cascade Properties, Inc., Lake Tarleton, NH, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Boise-Cascade Properties, Inc., Hawaii, HI, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Bristol Venture, Canandaigua, NY, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Cacadon State Park, WV, 1970 and 1971 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Calaveras Land Co., Inc., Calaveras County, CA, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - California Exposition, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - California, City of Fairfield, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - California, City of Mountain View, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - California, City of San Diego, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - California, City of San Joaquin, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - California Golf Club, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Canoe Brook Country Club, NJ, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Cape Land Development Co., West Falmouth, MA, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Carolina Trace - 4th Nine, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Carolina Trace - Sandhill Properties, Inc., Sanford, NC, 1971 and 1977 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Carowinds, Inc. - 18 Holes, Mecklenburg, NC, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Castle Leslie Golf Course, Ireland - Lawrence Mott, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Castle Leslie Golf Course, Ireland - International Planners Ltd., 1969 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Castle Leslie Golf Course, Ireland - International Planners Ltd., 1969 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Celebrity Country Club, Tulsa, OK, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Celebrity Country Club, Tulsa, OK, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Cella, Barr, Evans and Associates, Tucson, AZ, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Chubb and Son, Inc., Short Hills, NJ, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - College of the Virgin Islands, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Colonie, NY, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Cold Springs Country Club, Cold Springs Harbor, Long Island, NY, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Crestmont Country Club, West Orange, NY, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Cresview Country Club, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Crow, Pope and Carter Enterprises, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club, Barnardston, MA, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club, Barnardston, MA, 1969 and 1972 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Deal Country Club, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Domino's Farms, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Corporation, Puerto Rico, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Dow Market Realty, Miami, FL, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - The Dunes Golf and Beach, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Eagle County Development Corporation, Kawai, HI, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Falcon's Lair, Ltd., Mesquite, TX, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Fiji - Pacific Hotels and Developments Ltd., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Firestone Tire and Rubber Co., Akron, OH, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Folly Hill Associates, Beverly, MA, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Fort Gordon, GA, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Frankfurt Country Club. Frankfurt, KY, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Frates Communities, Inc., LBJ Ranch, TX, 1974 and 1975 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Glen Ridge Country Club, Glen Ridge, NJ, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Golden Triangle, Anne Arundel County, MD - Carl J. Rasnic, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Goodyear-Wyckoff - Crag Burn Golf Course, Buffalo, NY, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - Grand Teton Lodge, Jackson Hole, WY, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - Great Gorge, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Great Gorge, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - The Greensboro Jaycees, Greensboro, NC, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - Gulf American Corporation, River Ranch Shores, FL, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - Gulf American Corporation, Desert Lakes, FL, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - Hazeltine National Golf Club, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Hazeltine National Golf Club, Jonathan Development Corporation, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Hollywood Golf Course, Deal, NJ, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 71)
    - Horseshoe Bay, TX - Lake Lyndon B. Johnson Improvement Corporation, 1976 and 1981 (Box 30, Folder 72)
    - Horseshoe Bay, TX - Lake Lyndon B. Johnson Improvement Corporation, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 73)
    - Horseshoe Bay, TX - Lake Lyndon B. Johnson Improvement Corporation, 1972 and 1976 (Box 30, Folder 74)
    - Howard, Ted and Post, Tevy, Acapulco, Mexico, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 75)
    - International Resorts Inc., Birmingham, AL, 1970 and 1972 (Box 30, Folder 76)
    - Ipswich, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 77)
    - Iverson, Bucks County, PA, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 78)
    - Johns-Manville Idaho and Dollar Mountain Co., Blaine County, ID, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 79)
    - Karl Hope, East Stroudsburg, PA, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 80)
    - Lakewood Recreational Public Utility District of Humphreys and Houston Counties, TN, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 81)
    - Las Colinas Corp., Dallas County, TX, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 82)
    - Leeward, Inc., Mandham Boro, NJ, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 83)
    - Lido Golf Club, NY, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 84)
    - Lysander, NY, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 85)
    - Lysander, NY, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 86)
    - Mailman Development Corporation, Broward County, FL, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 87)
    - Malong Golf Course, Malone, NY, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 88)
    - Maryland Marine Properties, Inc., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 89)
    - Massachusetts Department of Civil Service and Registration, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 90)
    - Massanutten, Inc., Hopkins Spring, VA, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 91)
    - Melling Resorts International Inc., Gaylord, MI, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 92)
    - Midway Investment Corporation, AL, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 93)
    - Multicon Properties, Inc., Hilldale, IL, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 94)
    - Murrieta Hot Springs, Riverside County, CA, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 95)
    - National Ventures Trust, Topsfield, MA, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 96)
    - National Ventures Trust, Topsfield, MA, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 97)
    - Ocean City, NJ - Kinsky Associates, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 98)
    - Omaha Country Club, Omaha, NE, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 99)
    - Pocantico Hills Golf Course, NY, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 100)
    - Pope and Talbot Development Inc., Jefferson County, WA, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 101)
    - Portland, City of, OR, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 102)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 103)
    - Project Debra, Orange County, FL, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 104)
    - The Rail, Springfield, IL - Leonard Sapp and Jacob Bunn, Jr, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 105)
    - The Rail, Springfield, IL, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 106)
    - Salem Country Club, Peabody, MA, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 107)
    - SMS (IBM), Poughkeepsie, NY, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 108)
    - Stouffer's Fox Run, Bloomfield Hills, MI, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 109)
    - Transcentury Properties Inc., Bodega Harbor, CA, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 110)
    - United States Air Force - Elmendorf Air Force Base, AL, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 111)
    - Contracts and agreements (Box 40)
  - Completed Jobs
    - Crumpin Fox, 1987-1992 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Cornell, 1988-1991 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Deerwood Pointe, 1983-1991 (Box 102, Folder 3-5)
    - Dorado Beach, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Earltown Corp, 1985-1990 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Falcon's Lair Golf Course, 1984-1987 (Box 102, Folder 8-9)
    - France, Chamonix Plan, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Horseshoe Bay Publicity (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Fresco Enterprises, 1986-1991 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Great Gorge Village, 1986-1988 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Grand Beach, 1984-1988 (Box 102, Folder 14-16)
    - Ipswich, 1984-1989 (Box 102, Folder 17-20)
    - The Legends (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Aronimink Country Club, New Town, PA (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club, Barnardston, MA, 1987-1990 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - CYD Japan Company, Ltd., 1992-1994 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Eugene Country Club, Eugene, OR, 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Great Gorge Village Golf Course, McAffee, NJ, 1987-1989 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Jasna Polana, Princeton, NJ, 1991-1993 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - The Legends, Eureka, MO, 1987-1992 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Lely Flamingo Island Club, Naples, FL, 1990-1991 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Lely Flamingo Island Club, Naples, FL, 1988-1989 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Lely Flamingo Island Club, Naples, FL, 1985-1988 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Lely Flamingo Island Club, Naples, FL, 1987-1990 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Liberty State Park, NJ, 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Malone Golf Club, Malone, NY, 1985-1992 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Malone Golf Club, Malone, NY, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Malone Golf Club, Malone, NY, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Malone Golf Club, Malone, NY, 1983-1985 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Metedeconk National Golf Course, Jackson Township, NJ, 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Metedeconk National Golf Course, Jackson Township, NJ - Jackson Township/Sambol, 1982-1985 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Metedeconk National Golf Course, Jackson Township, NJ - Publicity, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Metedeconk National Golf Course, Jackson Township, NJ, 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Metedeconk National Golf Course, Jackson Township, NJ - Publicity, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - MetroWest Golf Course, Orlando, FL, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - MetroWest Golf Course, Orlando, FL, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - MetroWest Golf Course, Orlando, FL, 1984-1986 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Oak Hill Country Club, Rochester, NY, 1950-1989 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1975-1983 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1981-1982 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1989-1992 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - All Billing, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1979-1983 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic - Marketing Study Information, 1973-1974 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Playa Dorada Golf Course, Dominican Republic, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Point O'Woods Golf Course and Country Club, Benton Harbor, MI, 1986-1988 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Rancho Malibu, CA, 1987-1991 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - RP Farms Inc., Baltimore, MD, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Round Hill Golf Course, S. Dartmouth, MA, 1985-1988 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Ruggiero, Ron, 1985-1988 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Santa Maria Golf Club, Baton Rouge, LA, 1986-1990 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Santa Maria Golf Club, Baton Rouge, LA, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Santa Maria Golf Club, Baton Rouge, LA - Legal Papers [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Seabrook Island - Crooked Oaks Golf Course, Charleston, SC, 1981-1983 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Seabrook Island - Crooked Oaks Golf Course, Charleston, SC, 1976-1980 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Shady Oaks Country Club, Fort Worth, TX, 1981-1983 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Treetop Sylvan Resort, Gaylord, MI, 1987-1991 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Treetop Sylvan Resort, Gaylord, MI, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Army Navy club, 1983 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Mr. Di Gi (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Aronimink, 1989-1991 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Aronimink Golf Club, 1988-1992 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Cacapon State Park, 1971-1973 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Cacapon State Park, 1969-1970 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - West Virginia workmen's comp, 1971 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Cacapon State Park forms, 1971 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Cacapon, West Virginia, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Carolina Trace, 1971-1980 (Box 212, Folder 10-13)
    - Carolina Trace, Sanford, 1969-1972 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Carolina Trace sandhill properties (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Celebrity CC Courier, 1985 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Celebrity Country Club (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Celebrity Country Club, 1982-1988 (Box 212, Folder 18-20)
    - Island Horizons Company (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous RTJ (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - Breckenridge Eureka Associates, MO, 1985 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Houston Country Club (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Metro West, FL, 1985-1986 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Mountain View Golf Course, Hunterdon County, NJ, 1983-1985 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Point O'Woods Golf Course and Country Club, Benton Harbor, MI, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Prickly Pear Hill Golf Course, Croton-on-Hudson, NY, 1989-1994 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Prickly Pear Hill Golf Course, Croton-on-Hudson, NY, 1991-1992 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Prickly Pear Hill Golf Course, Croton-on-Hudson, NY, 1990-1992 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Rancho California - Walker Basin, Temecula, CA, 1990-1991 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Smith Mountain Lake, VA - Deerwood Pointe Golf Course, 1987-1989 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Chicago, IL - Orland Park - Rich Skrodzki, 1987-1988 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Dorado, Puerto Rico - Cerromar, 1985-1989 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Easton Golf Community, Easton, CT, 1991 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower Golf Course, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Grand Beach Golf Course, Galveston, TX, 1986 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Hazeltine, Chaska, MN, 1985-1986 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Ipswich Country Club, Ipswich, MA, 1986-1992 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Oakmont Country Club, Oakmont, PA, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Robert Trent Jones International Golf Club, Gainesville, VA, 1985-1993 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Santa Maria, Baton Rouge, LA, 1985-1987 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Tree Tops, Gaylord, MI, 1985-1988 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Wigwam Golf Course, Litchfield Park, AZ, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Yellowstone Country Club, MT, 1986 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Dead Leads, 1989-1991 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Dead Leads, 1989-1990 (Box 216, Folder 15)
  - Incomplete Jobs
    - Northern Lights, 1951-1961 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - North Shore (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - North Shore Olympic Swim Club (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nut Tree Golf Club (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Oakcreek Country Club (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Ocean County Golf Club (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Omaha Country Club (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Orchard Park Country Club, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Orchard Park, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Palm Bay Club, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Palmer Development Corp., 1969 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Paterson Club of Westport, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Patrick Air Force Base, 1958-1961 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia CC, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia CC, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Piping Rock Club, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Plantation Golf Course, 1974-1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Playa Grande, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Playa Grande, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Playa Dorada (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Playa Grande, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Notebooks (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Green Details (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sketches (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Three Island CC, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Three Island CC publicity, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Three Point Reports (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Three Point Mr. Searles, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Treasure Hills Country Club, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Treasure Hills Country Club, 1982-1984 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Treasure Hills brochures (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - University of Michigan, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Vail Associates, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Valley Landscape, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Veteran Isles Yacht Club (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Village Golf Course, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - College of the Virgin Islands, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 13-16)
    - Virginia Iron, Coal and Coke, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Wabeek Farms, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 18-19)
    - Washingtonian Country Club (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Werner, Mr. Mort (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - West Delta Park, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Wellesley Country Club, MA, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Westmoreland Country Club, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Wianno Golf Club, Osterville, MA, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Wilton Connecticut, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Winding Brook, 1964-1972 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Wolfner Properties, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - World Resorts Limited, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Lead Florida, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Fairfield Country club, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Folly Hill, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Forsgate Country Club, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Four Seasons, 1981-1986 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Fox Run, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Freeport, Grand Bahama Island, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Frankfort Country Club, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Lead Florida Green-Tree, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Guadaloupe, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Gulf American River Ranch Shores, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Gulf American Rio Rico, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Golf American Desert, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Hacienda Country Club, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Lead Maryland Hagerstown, 1975-1976 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Harrah Industries, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - American Golf Course Construction Co. vs. Bellamy (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Hawaii, Dillingham, Kona, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Higbee Mill Country Club and American Golf Course Construction Company contract (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Higbee Mill Country Club, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Higbee Mills Country Club, Bellamy, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Holmdel Golf and Country Club, 1984-1986 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Hunting Creek, 1969-1970 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Indiana Santa Claus Land, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Indonesia, Bali, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Franklin Field Property, 1966-1973 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Towpath Village, 1966-1971 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Quail Hollow, Ohio, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Iverson, 1965-1970 (Box 83, Folder 29-34)
    - Lead Jamaica Roaring River, 1973-1975 (Box 83)
    - Lead Jamaica, Morales, 1970 (Box 83)
    - Jamaica, 1969 (Box 83)
    - Jewel, Pliny, III, 1967 (Box 83)
    - Massanutten Project, 1970-1972 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Mendham, New Jersey, 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Middeleer, Charles, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Micke Grove Golf Course, 1967-1971 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Mill Neck Property, 1961-1965 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Mount Greylock, 1971-1984 (Box 99, Folder 6-7)
    - Mount Hood Meadows Development, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Mount Vernon Golf and Country Club, 1963-1965 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Mount View, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Musser International, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - New Canaan Country Club, 1947-1963 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - New Orleans Country Club, 1959-1962 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - New Jersey Mountain Lakes, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - New Jersey Sparta, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Newton Country Club, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - New York leads, 1980-1983 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Port Ludlow Golf Course, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Preston Lakes Country Club, 1972-1975 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Presidio Golf Club, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Puerto Rico, Arthur Finston, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Quail Hollow Country Club, 1959-1965 (Box 100, Folder 5-6)
    - Quaker Ridge Golf Club, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Quogue, New York, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Ranch on the Pedernales, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 9-10)
    - Reno-Vada Hotel and Golf Course, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Rhode Island Country Club, 1969-1972 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Rockleigh Bergen County golf, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Rolling Hills Country Club, 1969-1971 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Round Hill Club, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Royal Oaks Country Club, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Sakonnet Golf Club, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - San Gabriel Country Club, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - CBR Active Job: Sao Paulo, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Sedge Island, New Jersey, 1960-1961 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Shanty Creek Lodge, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Shawnee Country Club, 1973-1977 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Southern Illinois University, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Sparta, New Jersey, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Spaulding and Slye, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Spring Meadow, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Stowe, Vermont, 1956-1963 (Box 100, Folder 27-28)
    - Sugar Creek, 1975-1981 (Box 100, Folder 29-31)
    - Tahoe Keys, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - Tamblyn Associates, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - Tellride, 1979-1986 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - Tesuque Project, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - Klebary Country Club, 1966-1967 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - Lake Forest, 1959-1965 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - Lakepointe Country Club, 1958-1960 (Box 102, Folder 24-25)
    - Lake Tarleton, 1969-1971 (Box 102, Folder 26-27)
    - Killarney Golf Club, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Lake Wilderness Golf club, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - Las Colinas, 1961-1965 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - Abidjan (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Agadir Morocco (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Air Force Academy (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Ardsley Country Club (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Arrowhead Golf and Country Club (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Aspen Wild Cat (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic City (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Atlantic Beach (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Barberry Hills (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Belgium (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Beverly Ridge Estates (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Deal Golf and Country Club (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Devil's Nest, Nebraska (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Lead Dominican Republic (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Beverly Hills Country Club (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Blue Ridge Inn (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Bogota, Colombia (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Bonny Doon (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Braen Sand and Gravel (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Brookhaven, NY - Michael Steinhauer, 1969-1970 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Brookhaven, NY - Michael Steinhauer - Feasibility Study, 1967 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Burning Tree Club, Bethesda, MD, 1958-1966 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Calavweras Land Company, Inc., Stockton, CA - Louis Papais, Pres., 1971 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Carmel California, Mr. Edgar H. Haber - Monterey, 1962 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Carson City, NV, 1967-1970 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Carson Meadows, Carson City, NV - Ted Goldbeck, 1963-1966 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Cincinnati Country Club, Cincinnati, OH, 1964-1965 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland, OH - Paul Warren, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Colts Neck 1978 Report, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Colts Neck Newspaper Clippings, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Colts Neck, NJ, 1975-1982 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Colwell - Leads, 1966-1967 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Crystal Bay Development Co., Lake Tahoe, CA, 1963 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Curacao, N.A. - Ben Schmidt, 1963-1967 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Deal Gold and Country Club, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Dominican Republic, Ciudad, Trujillo - Pamphlets, 1958-1960 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - The Dunes, Myrtle Beach, SC, 1975-1976 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - The Dunes, Myrtle Beach, SC, 1977 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Duke University, Durham, NC, 1953-1962 (Box 190, Folder 20)
    - Dunwoodie Golf Course, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - Dunwoodie Golf Course, 1979-1980 (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - DuPont Property, Qualls, MD, 1965-1968 (Box 190, Folder 23)